<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
    <addon id="aTiLaRePo" name="aTiLaRePo" version="0.4.0" provider-name="aTiLa">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="aTiLaRePo">
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/atilaprieto/aTiLaRePo/master/_repo/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/atilaprieto/aTiLaRePo/master/_repo/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/atilaprieto/aTiLaRePo/master/_repo/</datadir>
            <hashes>false</hashes>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary>Respositorio de aTiLa</summary>
            <description>aTiLa Pri Repository</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="inputstream.adaptive"
  version="2.4.6"
  name="InputStream Adaptive"
  provider-name="peak3d">
  <requires>
<import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.global.general" version="1.0.3"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.global.filesystem" version="1.0.2"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.instance.inputstream" version="2.0.8"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.instance.videocodec" version="1.0.1"/></requires>
  <extension
    point="kodi.inputstream"
    name="adaptive"
    extension=""
    tags="true"
    listitemprops="license_type|license_key|license_data|license_flags|manifest_type|server_certificate|stream_headers|manifest_update_parameter|original_audio_language|media_renewal_url|media_renewal_time|max_bandwidth|play_timeshift_buffer"
    library_windows="inputstream.adaptive.dll"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">InputStream client for adaptive streams</summary>
	<summary lang="es">Cliente InputStream para flujo de datos adaptativos</summary>
    <description lang="en">InputStream client for adaptive streams</description>
	<description lang="es">Cliente InputStream para flujo de datos adaptativos</description>
    <platform>windows-x86_64</platform>
	<news>
v2.4.6 (2020-05-18)
- Fix effective url if paths beginning with / provided
- Several translations added / fixed
- Fix webvtt subtitles for time formats without leading hour 00:
- Fix segfault when playing PlayReady content (Android)

v2.4.5 (2020-05-18)
- Backport of Matrix features (v2.5.4 upwards)

v2.4.3 (2020-02-25)
- Backport of Matrix features (v2.5.0 upwards)

v2.4.2 (2019-09-02)
- Fix versioning

v2.3.22 (2019-06-14)
- Bento4: sample duration workaround (24/1)
- WVDecrypter: remove sleep between decrypt calls

v2.3.21 (2019-06-07)
- [DASH] initialize segment::range_begin_ for URL segments (youtube)

v2.3.20 (2019-06-07)
- Fix parsing PR ContentProtection KID

v2.3.19 (2019-06-02)
- [widevine] remove API 8 / Add API 11
- [TS] Signal configuration change if extra-data has changed
- [DASH] Use PlayReady WRMHEADER to retrieve DefaultKID
- [DASH] Allow URL_SEGMENTS + Range-Bytes

v2.3.18 (2019-05-11)
- align settings with internal resolution check
- [HLS] support single playlists

v2.3.17 (2019-04-16)
- Fix KID's with 0 char inside

v2.3.16 (2019-03-25)
- TTML parser fix
- [HLS] Add HEVC streams / Fix extra_data_size in ts parser
- [HLS] effective URL for license

v2.3.15 (2019-02-11)
- Fix windows build

v2.3.14 (2019-02-10)
- Add WebM container parser
	</news>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.themoviedb.org"
       name="The Movie Database Scraper Library"
       version="3.2.16"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="tmdb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="en">TMDb Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de peliculas de TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">TMDb elokuvatietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">TMDb leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">TMDb-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обработчик для TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapebibliotek för TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">TMDb刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля миниатюри и fanarts от www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="en">Download thumbs and fanarts from www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga posters y fanart de www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa pienoiskuvia ja fanitaidetta www.themoviedb.org -sivustolta</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharge vignettes et backdrops depuis www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="hu">Bélyeg- és fanartképek letöltése a www.themoviedb.org webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Miniaturen en fanart ophalen van www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj ikony i fanarty z www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descărcați miniaturi și imagini realizate de fani de pe www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать миниатюры и фанарт с www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner miniatyrer och fanart från www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.themoviedb.org下载海报和同人画</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.themoviedb.org"
       name="The Movie Database"
       version="5.2.1"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.imdb.com" version="2.9.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.themoviedb.org" version="3.2.0"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="4.4.10" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.movies"
             language="en"
             library="tmdb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">TMDB Fliek Skraper</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Сваля инф. за филми от TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Arreplegador de pel·lícules TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Stahovač informací k filmům z TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Crafwr Ffilmiau TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">TMDB Scraper til Film</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">TMDB Filmscraper</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Scraper Ταινιών του TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Scraper de películas de TheMovieDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper de Películas de TheMovieDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper de Películas TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">TMDB Filmi kaabits</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">TMDB elokuvatietojen lataaja</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Collecteur de Films TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur de films TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Scraper de Filme de TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">TMDB סקרייפר סרטים</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">TMDB filmski sakupljač informacija</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">TMDB filmadat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Pengais Film TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">TMDB Skafa fyrir Kvikmyndir</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Ricercatore per TMDB Movie</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">TMDB映画のスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">TMDB 영화 정보수집기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">TMDB filmų skreperis</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">TMDB инфо за филмови</summary>
    <summary lang="ml_IN">മൂവി ഡി ബി, വിവരശേഖരം</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Pengikis Cakera TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="my_MM">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">TMDb-filmscraper</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">TMDB-skraper</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Ekstraktor filmowy TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Colector de filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper de Filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Scraper de filme TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Инфоресурс на базе TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">TheMovieDB filmový sťahovač</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Ponudnik informacij o filmih TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">TMDB Filmskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">LastFM நிகழ்படம் சுரண்டி</summary>
    <summary lang="th_TH">ตัวรับข้อมูลภาพยนต์ TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">TMDB Film Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">TMDB — джерело інформації про фільми</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Trình lấy dữ liệu Phim từ TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">TMDB 电影刮削器</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">TMDB 電影搜括器</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">themoviedb.org is 'n verniet en oop fliek databasis. Dit is totaal gebruiker gedryf deur mense soos jy. TMDB word huidiglik deur miljoene mense elke maand gebruik, en met hulle kragtige API word dit ook deur baie gewilde media sentrums soos Kodi gebruik om Fliek Metadata, Plakkate en Ondersteunerkuns te onttrek om die gebruiker se ondervinding te verryk.</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">themoviedb.org е безплатна и отворена филмова база данни. Задвижва се изцяло от потребителите си, от хора като вас. Милиони хора по света всеки месец ползват TMDb. Благодарение на многофункционално API може да се ползва от най-различни и популярни медийни центрове като Kodi, които извличат метаданни, постери и фанарт за филми с цел за красивото оформяне на интерфейса.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">themoviedb.org és una base de dades oberta i lliure. Es manté completament per usuaris, per gent com tu. TMDb s'utilitza actualment per milions de persones cada mes i amb la seva potent API també és utilitzada per molts centre media populas com l'Kodi per obtenir les meta-dades de pel·lícules, pósters i fanart per enriquir l'experiència d'usuari.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">themoviedb.org je bezplatná a otevřená databáze filmů a seriálů. Je celá řízena uživateli, tedy lidmi jako vy. TMDb je aktuálně používána každý měsíc milióny lidí a se svým výborným API je také používána mnoha oblíbenými multimediálními centry, jako je Kodi, k získávání metadat, plakátů a fanartů filmů a seriálů pro obohacení uživatelského zážitku.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mae themoviedb.org yn gronfa ddata ffilmiau rhydd ac agored. Mae'n cael ei yrru gan ddefnyddwyr fel chi. Mae TMDb yn cael ei ddefnyddio gan filiynau o bobl bob mis a gyda'i API pwerus, mae'n cael ei ddefnyddio gan lawer o'r canolfannau cyfrwng fel Kodi i estyn metadata ffilmiau, posteri a chelf er mwyn cyfoethogi profiad defnyddwyr.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">themoviedb.org er en fri og åben filmdatabase. Den er helt og aldeles brugerdrevet af folk som dig. TMDb bruges i dag af millioner af mennesker hver måned, og med deres kraftfulde API er den også brugt af mange populære mediecentre såsom Kodi til at hente metadata, plakater og fankunst til film, for at berige brugerens oplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">TheMovieDB.org ist eine freie und offene Filmdatenbank. Sie wird von Benutzern wie dir angetrieben. TheMovieDB wird zur Zeit von millionen Nutzern jeden Monat genutzt und dank ihrer mächtigen API ist sie auch von vielen Media-Center, wie z.B. Kodi, implementiert, um Film-Metadaten, -Poster und -Fanarts zu beziehen, die das Benutzererlebnis verbessern.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Το themoviedb.org είναι μία δωρεάν και ανοικτή βάση δεδομένων ταινιών. Διαχειρίζεται πλήρως από ανθρώπους σαν και εσάς. Το TMDb χρησιμοποιείται από εκατομμύρια ανθρώπους κάθε μήνα, και με το πανίσχυρο API τους, χρησιμοποιείται και από πολλά δημοφιλή κέντρα πολυμέσων όπως το Kodi για να λαμβάνουν μετα-δεδομένα Ταινιών, Αφίσες και Fanart για εμπλουτισμό της εμπειρίας του χρήστη.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Es una página web que se basa en contenido subido por los usuarios. TMDb es usada diariamente por mucha gente gracias a su API, que es usada por más programas aparte de Kodi para descargar información de películas así como Posters o Fanart (Fondos de escritorio basados en películas usados en distintos skins) para enriquecer la experiencia de usar Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Está  formada con contenido subido por usuarios como vos. TMDb es actualmente utilizada por millones de personas cada mes y, gracias a su poderosa API, es usada por muchos programas populares como Kodi para descargar Información de Películas, Posters y Fanart para enriquecer la experiencia de usar Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">themoviedb.org es una base de datos de películas gratis y abierta. Es completamente manejada por usuarios y personas como tu. Actualmente TMDb es usada por millones de personas cada mes, y dado a su poderosa API, es usada también por varios media centers populares como Kodi para obtener Metada de Películas, Posters y Fanarts, enriqueciendo de esta manera la experiencia del usuario.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">themoviedb.org on tasuta ja vaba juurdepääsuga filmide andmebaas.See on täielikult koostatud sinu sarnaste inimeste poolt. TMDb on hetkel igapäevaselt kasutuses miljonite inimeste poolt ja seda kasutavad paljud populaarsed meediakeskused, nagu ka Kodi, filmiandmete, fännikunsti ja posterite leidmiseks.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">themoviedb.org on vapaa ja avoin elokuvatietokanta. Se on täysin käyttäjien ylläpitämä. TMDb:a käyttää miljoonat ihmiset joka kuukausi, sitä käytetään käyttäjäkokemuksen rikastuttamiseen monissa muissakin suosituissa Kodi:n kaltaisissa ohjelmissa lataamalla elokuvien tietoja, julisteita ja fanitaidetta.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">themoviedb.org est une base de données gratuite et libre d'accès de films. Elle est totalement gérée par les utilisateurs. TMDb est actuellement utilisée par des millions de personnes chaque mois et, grâce à ses puissantes fonctions et routines, elle est également utilisée par de nombreux Media Centers populaires comme Kodi aux fins de récupération des Métadonnées, Posters et Fanarts des films en vue d'améliorer l'expérience de l'utilisateur.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">themoviedb.org est une base de données libre et ouverte. Elle est complètement gérée par des gens comme vous. TMDb est actuellement utilisée par des millions de personnes chaque mois et avec son API puissante, elle est également utilisée par de nombreux centres multimédias populaires comme Kodi pour récupérer les métadonnées des films, les affiches et le fanart afin d'enrichir l'expérience de l'utilisateur.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">themoviedb.org é una base de datos sobre filmes libre e aberta, impulsada por xente coma ti. Na actualidade TMDb é usada por millóns de persoas todos os meses, e grazas ó seu potente API, usado por algúns dos centros multimedia máis populares como Kodi para obter a información dos filmes, Posters e Fanart e así mellorar a experiencia do usuario.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">themoviedb.org je besplatna i otvorena baza filmskih podataka. TMDb trenutno koriste milijuni ljudi svaki mjesec uz pomoću njegovog snažnog API-ja, isto tako se koristi u mnogim popularnim medijskim centrima poput Kodi-a, kako bi mogli sakupljati informacije o filmovima, filmske postere, omote filmova i na kraju obogatili korisničko iskustvo.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">A themoviedb.org egy ingyenes és nyílt filmadatbázis. Teljes egészében olyan felhasználók töltik fel, mint például Te. A TMDb-t havonta emberek milliói használják és a hatékony API-n keresztül számos népszerű média center is, mint például az Kodi a filmadatok, poszterek, fanartképek letöltésére.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">themoviedb.org adalah database film yang gratis dan terbuka. Ini benar-benar digerakkan oleh orang-orang seperti Anda. TMDb saat ini digunakan oleh jutaan orang setiap bulannya dan dengan APInya yang digdaya, juga digunakan oleh beberapa pusat media seperti Kodi untuk mengambil Metadata Film, Poster dan Fanart untuk menperkaya pengalaman penggunanya.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">themoviedb.org er frír og opinn gagnagrunnur. Hann er algjörlega rekinn af fólki eins og þér. TMBd er notaður af milljónum manna í hverjum mánuði og með öflugum forritaskilum þeirra (API), er hann líka notaður af mörgum vinsælum heimabíókerfum eins og Kodi til að ná í Ítarupplýsingar yfir Kvikmyndir, Veggspjöld og Fanart til að lífga upplifun notandans.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">themoviedb.org è un database libero e aperto. E' gestito da utenti e persone come te. Viene usato correntemente da millioni di persone ogni mese e con le sue potenti API, è anche utilizzato da molti popolari media centers come Kodi per ottenere Metadati, Posters e Fanart di film per arricchire la loro esperienza utente.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">themoviedb.org は自由でオープンな映画データベースです。その運営は、完全にユーザ主導で行われています。TMDb は現在毎月何百万人もの人に利用されているほか、Kodi のようなメディアセンターも、TMDb のパワフルな API を介して映画メタデータ、ポスター、ファンアートを取得し、使い勝手を向上させるなどして使っています。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">themoviedb.org 는 전적으로 여러분 같은 이용자가 주도하는 무료 공개 영화 데이터베이스입니다. TMDb 는 현재 매월 수백만의 사람들이 강력한 API와 함께 사용하고 있을 뿐만 아니라 Kodi 같은 많은 미디어 센터가 영화 정보, 포스터, 팬아트를 가져와 풍성한 사용자 경험을 제공하는데 이용되고 있습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">themoviedb.org yra nemokama ir atvira filmų duomenų bazė. Ji palaikoma tokių pat vartotojų kaip ir jūs. TMDb šiuo metu naudojama milijonų žmonių kiekvieną mėnesį ir turi galingą API, o taip pat naudojama daugelio populiarių media centrų, tokių kaip Kodi, kad gautų filmų metaduomenis, plakatus ir Fanart, siekiant praturtinti vartotojo patirtį.</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="ml_IN">മൂവി ഡി ബി, എല്ലാവർക്കും കൈവക്കാവുന്ന ഒരു സൗജന്യ വിവരശേഖരമാണ്. ഇതുമൂലം ലോകം മുഴുവനും സിനിമാ പോസ്റ്ററുകൾ എല്ലവരും കാണുന്നു</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">themoviedb.org adalah pangkalan data cakera terbuka. Ia sepenuhnya dipacu oleh individu seperti anda. TMDb buat masa ini diguna oleh berjuta-juta individu setiap bulan dan dengan API hebat mereka, ia juga digunakan oleh banyak pusat media popular seperti Kodi untuk mendapatkan Data Meta, Poster, Seni Peminat Cereka untuk memperkayakan pengalaman pengguna.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Themoviedb.org is een vrije en open filmdatabank. Gebruikers zoals jij vormen de motor van deze site. Op dit moment gebruiken elke maand miljoenen mensen TMDb. De krachtige API van de site laat mediacenters zoals Kodi toe om metadata, posters en fanart op te halen en zo de gebruikerservaring te verrijken.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">themoviedb.org er en fir og åpen filmdatabase. Den drives helt og fullt av mennesker som deg. TMDB brukes av millioner av mennesker hver måned og med sitt gode API, brukes den også av mange popluære mediasenterløsninger som Kodi for å hente metadata for filmer, plakater og fanart for å gi en bedre brukeropplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">themoviedb.org jest wolną i otwartą filmową bazą danych, zarządzaną przez osoby takie jak Ty. Obecnie odwiedzają ją miliony osób miesięcznie, a dzięki dostępności interfejsu programistycznego jest używana przez wiele centrów multimedialnych takich jak Kodi, jako źródło informacji o filmach, plakatów i tapet.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">O themoviedb.org é uma base de dados de filmes livre e aberta. É actualizado inteiramente por pessoas como você e usado por milhões todos os meses. Com o poderoso motor de busca disponível, também se tornou no favorito para muitos programas de centro de média, como o popular Kodi, para obter informação, posters e fanart que enriquecem a experiência do utilizador.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O themoviedb.org é um banco de dados aberto e gratuito. É completamente operado por pessoas como você. O TMDb é atualmente usado por milhares de pessoas a cada mês e com sua poderosa API, é usado por muitas centrais de mídia populares como o Kodi para buscar metadados, cartazes e fanart de filmes para enriquecer a experiência do usuário.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">themoviedb.org este o bază de date de filme gratuită și deschisă. Este actualizată de oameni ca și tine. TMDb este curent folosită de milioane de oameni în fiecare lună și datorită API-ului puternic, este de asemena folosită de multe centre media populare ca Kodi pentru a obține informații despre filme, afișe și imagini produse de fani (Fanart) care îmbogățesc experiența utilizatorului.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">themoviedb.org — это бесплатная и открытая база данных фильмов. Она полностью поддерживается обычными людьми. В данный момент сайт TMDb используют миллионы людей каждый месяц, и благодаря мощному API его могут использовать различные популярные медиацентры, такие как Kodi, чтобы получать метаданные, постеры и фанарт для фильмов с целью красивого оформления интерфейса.</description>
    <description lang="se">themoviedb.org är en fri och öppen filmdatabas. Det drivs helt av människor som dig. TMDb används av miljontals människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API, är det också använt av många populära mediacenter som Kodi för att hämta filmmetadata, omslag och fanart för att förgylla användarens upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">themoviedb.org je voľná a otvorená databáza filmov. Je výlučne vedená užívateľmi ako si ty. TMDb je každý mesiac používaná miliónmi ľudí, a vďaka svojmu výkonnému API je veľmi populárna medzi 'media centrami' ako Kodi pre sťahovanie filmových metadát, plagátov a fanartov pre obohatenie  zážitkov.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">themoviedb.org je brezplačna in prosta baza filmov. Je v celoti ustvarjena s strani uporabnikov kot ste vi. TMDB uporablja miljone ljudi in z njihovo močno API, jo lahko uporabljate tudi v multimedijskih centrih kot Kodi, s tem prenesete informacije o filmih, plakate in ozadja ter s tem popestrite uporabniško izkušnjo.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">themoviedb.org är en gratis och öppen filmdatabas. Den drivs helt av människor som du. TMDb används för närvarande av miljoner människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API används den även av många populära mediacenter som t.ex. Kodi för att hämta metadata om filmer, affischer och fanart för att berika användarens upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">themoviedb.org ஒரு இலவச மற்றும் திறந்த திரைப்பட தரவுத்தளம் ஆகும். இந்த தரவுத்தளம்  முற்றிலும் பயனர் மக்களால் இயக்கப்படுகிறது. TMDb அவர்களது சக்திவாய்ந்த API இனால் தற்போது பல இலட்சக்கணக்கான மக்களால் ஒவ்வொரு மாதமும் பயன்படுத்தப்படுகிறது, இது Kodi போன்ற பல பிரபல ஊடக மையங்களில் பயனர் அனுபவத்தை மேம்படுத்த பயன்படுத்தப்படுகிறது.</description>
    <description lang="th_TH">themoviedb.org เป็นฐานข้อมูลภาพยนตร์ที่ฟรีและเปิดกว้าง. มันถูกขับเคลื่อนจากผู้ใช้ โดยคนเช่นคุณ. TMDb ปัจจุบันมีการใช้โดยคนนับล้านในแต่ละเดือน และมีประสิทธิภาพด้วย API ของพวกเขา , มันยังถูกใช้โดยหลายศูนย์สื่อที่นิยมเช่น Kodi เพื่อดึง อธิบายข้อมูลภาพยนตร์, โปสเตอร์และ แฟนอาร์ต เพื่อเพิ่มประสบการณ์ของผู้ใช้</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">themoviedb.org ücretsiz ve herkese açık bir film veri tabanıdır. Tamamen kullanıcılar tarafından oluşturulmakta ve yönetilmektedir. TMDb her ay milyonlarca kullanıcı tarafından kullanılmakta ve güçlü API'si sayesinde Kodi gibi bir çok popüler medya merkezi tarafından Film Veritabanı, Poster ve Fanart bilgilerini kullanarak kullanıcı deneyimini zenginleştirmektedir.</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">themoviedb.org - це безкоштовна і відкрита база даних фільмів. Вона повністю підтримується звичайними людьми. В даний момент сайт TMDb використовують мільйони людей кожен місяць, і завдяки потужному API, його можуть використовувати різні популярні медіацентри, такі як Kodi, щоб отримувати метадані, постери і фанарт для фільмів з метою оформлення інтерфейсу.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">themoviedb.org là cơ sở dữ liệu về phim ảnh mở và miễn phí. Nó hoàn toàn được kiểm soát bởi những người như bạn. TMDb hiện tại đang được sử dụng bởi hàng triệu người dùng hàng tháng và với sự hỗ trợ của bộ API mạnh mẽ nó cũng được sử dụng bởi những thiết bị giải trí cá nhân như Kodi cho việc lấy dữ liệu về Phim ảnh, Poster và Fanart để làm tăng trải nghiệm của người sử dụng</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">themoviedb.org 是一个开放和自由的电影数据库。它完全由象你一样的用户来掌控。TMDb 每月为上百万用户提供服务，并通过强大的 API 界面为许多流行的媒体中心系统如 Kodi 提供电影资料、封面海报和同人画以丰富用户的体验。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">themoviedb.org是一個免費和開放的電影資料庫。它是完全由與您一樣的廣大使用者來更新資訊。 TMDb目前擁有數以百萬計的使用人次並且有著強大的API，許多受歡迎的媒體中心平台像Kodi藉由TMDb獲取電影的數據資料庫，海報和影片資訊，以豐富使用者體驗。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL v2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=339672</forum>
    <website>https://www.themoviedb.org</website>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.googledrive" name="Google Drive" version="1.3.4" provider-name="Carlos Guzman (cguZZman)">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.clouddrive.common" version="1.2.12"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
		<provides>image audio video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Google Drive for KODI</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">
Play all your media from Google Drive including Videos, Music and Pictures (including Google Photos).
 - Unlimited number of accounts.
 - Team Drives support
 - Google Photos support
 - Search over your drive.
 - Auto-Refreshed slideshow.
 - Export your videos to your library (.strm files)
 - Use Google Drive as a source
 - This program is not affiliated with or sponsored by Google.
		</description>
		<summary lang="he_IL">כונן Google Drive של מיקרוסופט עבור קודי</summary>
		<description lang="he_IL">
הפעל את כל המדיה שלך מ- Google Drive כולל וידאו, מוסיקה ותמונות.
  - מספר בלתי מוגבל של חשבונות.
  - חיפוש ומציאת הכונן שלך.
  - ריענון מצגת אוטומטית.
  - ייצוא קטעי הווידאו לספרייה שלך (קבצי .strm)
  - שימוש ב-Google Drive כמקור
  - תוכנית זו אינה קשורה או ממומנת על ידי Google.
		</description>
		<license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
		<source>https://github.com/cguZZman/plugin.googledrive</source>
		<forum>https://github.com/cguZZman/plugin.googledrive/issues</forum>
		<website>https://addons.kodi.tv/show/plugin.googledrive</website>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news>
v1.3.4 released Mar 3, 2020:
- NFO export
		</news>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">
This cloud drive addon uses a third-party authentication mechanism commonly known as OAuth 2.0.
If you want to know more about OAuth 2.0 you can visit the following pages:
- https://oauth.net/2/
- https://developers.google.com/identity/protocols/OAuth2
- https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/onedrive/developer/rest-api/getting-started/msa-oauth

Kodi and myself take no responsibility or liability.

The authentication server URL is specified in Settings / Advanced / Sign-in Server. The Sign-in Server implements the OAuth 2.0 protocol.
The complete source code of the Sign-in Server can be download here: https://github.com/cguZZman/drive-login
You can clone the project and host it in your own server.
		</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.program.WiZaRTiLa" name="WiZaRTiLa" version="1.0.2" provider-name="aTiLa">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">WiZaRTiLa</summary>
    <description lang="en">Wizard para Kodi 18
    </description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.1x2"
  version="1.0.27"
  name="1x2"
  provider-name="Team NS">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.routing"/>
    <import addon="inputstream.adaptive" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube"/>
    <import addon="script.video.F4mProxy" version="2.8.8"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.f4mTester" version="2.7.2"/>
    <import addon="script.module.TvTap"/>
    <import addon="program.plexus"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="es">Los videos son proporcionados por personas ... en línea ... en algún lugar...</summary>
    <description lang="es">Los videos son proporcionados por personas ... en línea ... en algún lugar...</description>
    <disclaimer lang="es">El autor no almacena ni distribuye ninguno de los contenidos que se muestran en este addon. El autor no tiene ninguna afiliación con el proveedor de contenidos.</disclaimer>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.gif</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.alfa" name="Alfa" version="3.2.6" provider-name="Alfa Addon">
  <requires>
    <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.5.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.html5lib" version="0.999.0"/>
    <import addon="script.alfa-update-helper" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="es">Navega con Kodi por páginas web.</summary>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icono_3.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/halloween2020.png</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/media/themes/ss/1.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/themes/ss/2.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/themes/ss/3.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/media/themes/ss/4.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
      <news>[B]Estos son los cambios para esta versión:[/B]

      [COLOR green][B]Arreglos[/B][/COLOR]
      ¤ Dontorrent                                  ¤ Magnetpelis                               ¤ Newpct1
      ¤ Pctfenix                                        ¤ BlogHorror                                 ¤ Pelkex
      ¤ SeriesRetro                                  ¤ Cineclasicoonline                       ¤ Clubdecine
      ¤ Dangtoons                                  ¤ Fullseriehd                                  ¤ Pepecine
      ¤ Hdfull                                           ¤ Movidy                                        ¤ Shahid4u
      ¤ Cinehindi                                     ¤ Cuevana3                                    ¤ Cinetux
      ¤ 18+

      [COLOR green][B]Novedades[/B][/COLOR]
      ¤ Madeintorrent                            ¤ Doramedplay                             ¤ CinemaT4

      Agradecimientos a @DamianBacalov por su colaboración en esta versión

    </news>
    <description lang="es">Navega con Kodi por páginas web para ver sus videos de manera fácil.</description>
    <summary lang="en">Browse web pages using Kodi</summary>
    <description lang="en">Browse web pages using Kodi, you can easily watch their video content.</description>
    <disclaimer>[COLOR red]The owners and submitters to this addon do not host or distribute any of the content displayed by these addons nor do they have any affiliation with the content providers.[/COLOR]</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GPL v3</license>
    <forum>foro</forum>
    <website>web</website>
    <email>my@email.com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/alfa-addon/addon</source>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="videolibrary_service.py" start="login|startup">
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.atresplayer" name="ATRESPLAYER" version="1.4.2" provider-name="Hiraya Software">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
		<import addon="script.module.resolveurl" />
		<import addon="plugin.video.f4mTester" />
		<import addon="script.video.F4mProxy" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Hiraya Software Repo">
		<info>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://hirayasoftware.github.io/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">ATRESPLAYER</summary>
		<description lang="en">ATRESPLAYER Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Addon con la programación de ATRESPLAYER a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<summary lang="es">ATRESPLAYER</summary>
		<description lang="es">ATRESPLAYER Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Addon con la programación de ATRESPLAYER a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
        <website></website>
        <video_guide></video_guide>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.balandro" name="Balandro" version="2.0.2" provider-name="Balandro Team">
  <requires>
  </requires>

  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>

  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Balandro es un navegador de páginas webs</summary>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
    <news>
    [COLOR darkorange]Mayo 2021[/COLOR]
      Correcciones bugs de la version anterior
      Configuración opción Descartar búsquedas en canales torrent
      Nuevo proveedor de proxies: SilverProxies
      Buscar:
        Filmaffinitylists - cambio estructura
        Oscars 2021 - mejorado
        Descartar canales que pueden contener archivos torrent
      Canales modificados:
        AniBox, AnimeFenix, AnimeFlv, Beeg, CiberDocumentales,
        CineMatteFlix, ClasicoTv, Cliver, DocumaniaTv, DonTorrents,
        Estrenoscinesaa, HdFull, HdFullSe, InkaPelis, JKanime,
        LaCartoons, MegadedeLa, MejorTorrents, PctFenix, Pelis24,
        PelisVips, PornHub, PornTube, SeriesAntiguas, SeriesFlix,
        SeriesKao, SeriesLan, SeriesPapayaTo, SeriesPapayaXyz,
        SeriesRetro, SerieZ, Tekilaz, TorrentDivx, TuCineClasico,
        TupeliculaTv, TuPeliHd, VerPeliculasGratis, XVideos
      Canales desactivados:
        AllPeliculas, CineCalidad, PlayDede, RePelis, SeriesBlanco,
        SeriesFlv
      Canales nuevos:
        CumLouder, Hentaisd, MiraDeTodo, MiraPeliculas, MonosChinos,
        PelisGratis, PelisMaraton, PelisPlanet, PelisXd, SeriesAnimadas,
        TioAnime, Tubehentai
      Servidores modificados:
        Aparat, Clipwatching, Fembed, Gamovideo, Highstream, Mega,
        PlayTube, Sbembed, Uptobox, Streamsb, YourUpload
      Servidores nuevos:
        ShareVid
    [COLOR darkorange][B]Media Centers soportados[COLOR plum][I] Kodi 19.X, 18.X y 17.X [/I][/B][/COLOR]
    </news>
    <summary>Balandro es un navegador de páginas webs</summary>
    <description>[COLOR yellow][B]Balandro es un MOD derivado de Pelisalacarta y Alfa,[COLOR mediumaquamarine] y Tiene Como Objeto, Permitir Visualizar Películas, Series y Documentales, Todo a Través de Internet y Directamente Desde su Sistema Media Center. [COLOR orchid]Este Add-On es Tan Solo un Mero Ejercicio de Aprendizaje Del Lenguaje de Programación Python y se Distribuye Sin Ningún Contenido Multimedia Adjunto al Mismo [COLOR lightgrey][I]En Consecuencia Solo Las Webs Son Plenamente Responsables de Los Contenidos Que Publiquen.[/I][/B][/COLOR]</description>
    <disclaimer>[COLOR tan][B]Está Prohibida su Distribución, Solo o Junto Con Contenidos Multimedia Protegidos Por Los Derechos de Autor. [COLOR chocolate]Si Este Tipo de Contenido Está Prohibido en su País, Solamente Usted Será el Responsable de su Uso. [COLOR white]La Vulneración de Estas Prohibiciones Exonerarán de Cualquier Culpa a sus Autores, [COLOR red]Siendo el Único Responsable Quien lo Haya Distribuido o Utilizado Ilegalmente.[/B][/COLOR]</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GPL v3</license>
    <forum>https://www.mimediacenter.info/foro/viewforum.php?f=44</forum>
    <website>https://balandro.tk</website>
    <email>my@email.com</email>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="services.py" start="login|startup"/>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.canalsur" name="CANAL SUR" version="1.0.2" provider-name="Alex303 - Hiraya Software">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
		<import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="5.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Hiraya Software Repo">
		<info>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://hirayasoftware.github.io/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">CANAL SUR</summary>
		<description lang="en">CANAL SUR Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Addon con la programación de CANAL SUR a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<summary lang="es">CANAL SUR</summary>
		<description lang="es">CANAL SUR Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Addon con la programación de CANAL SUR a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
        <website></website>
        <video_guide></video_guide>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon
	id="plugin.video.chopocine" version="4" name="[B][COLOR white]CHOPO[COLOR gold]CINE[/COLOR][/B]" provider-name="equipo tvchopo">
	<requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
	<import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0"/>
	<import addon="script.module.pycryptodome" version="3.4.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="0.9.4"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    <import addon="script.module.httplib2" />
    <import addon="script.module.liveresolver" version="0.1.24" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.youtube.dl" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" />
    <import addon="script.module.urlresolver" />
	<import addon="script.module.resolveurl" optional="true"/>
	<import addon="script.module.simplejson" />
    <import addon="script.module.livestreamer" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pyamf" optional="true"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>

	 <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="tvchopo">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/</datadir>
    </extension>


	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
                <platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en">chopocine</summary>
		<summary lang="da">chopocine</summary>
		<description lang="en">[B][LOWERCASE][CAPITALIZE][COLOR white]addon de cine de la familia tvchopo[COLOR aqua]                   agradecimientos a jesus  de pelis a la carta por los tutoriales... a titan con sus ayudas y su codigo para los colores.. y a todos los que me hayan podido ayudar muchisimas gracias a todos                                                                     para cualquier consulta o problema  unete  a nuestro grupo de telegram [COLOR yellow]@tvchopo[/COLOR][/CAPITALIZE][/LOWERCASE][/B]</description>
		<website></website>
		<license>GPL 2.0</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
<assets>
        <icon>icon.gif</icon>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot1.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot2.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot3.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot4.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot5.jpg</screenshot>
        <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
    </assets>
		<language>es</language>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon
	id="plugin.video.choposeries" version="3.0" name="[B][COLOR white]CHOPO[COLOR gold]SERIES 3.0[/COLOR][/B]" provider-name="equipo tvchopo">
	<requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
	<import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0"/>
	<import addon="script.module.pycryptodome" version="3.4.3"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="0.9.4"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    <import addon="script.module.httplib2" />
    <import addon="script.module.liveresolver" version="0.1.24" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.youtube.dl" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" />
    <import addon="script.module.urlresolver" />
	<import addon="script.module.resolveurl" optional="true"/>
	<import addon="script.module.simplejson" />
    <import addon="script.module.livestreamer" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pyamf" optional="true"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>

	 <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="tvchopo">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/</datadir>
    </extension>


	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
                <platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en">choposeries</summary>
		<summary lang="da">choposeries</summary>
		<description lang="en">[B][LOWERCASE][CAPITALIZE][COLOR white]addon de series de la familia tvchopo[COLOR aqua]                   agradecimientos a jesus  de pelis a la carta por los tutoriales... a titan con sus ayudas y su codigo para los colores.. y a todos los que me hayan podido ayudar muchisimas gracias a todos                                                                     para cualquier consulta o problema  unete  a nuestro grupo de telegram [COLOR yellow]@tvchopo[/COLOR][/CAPITALIZE][/LOWERCASE][/B]</description>
		<website></website>
		<license>GPL 2.0</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
<assets>
        <icon>icon.gif</icon>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot1.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot2.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot3.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot4.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot5.jpg</screenshot>
        <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
    </assets>
		<language>es</language>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.cristalazul"
       name="[B][/B][COLOR aqua]CRISTAL AZUL[/COLOR]"
       version="0.0.12"
       provider-name="PICAPAU, LOURDES, SUPERTOPO, LUISMA">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="0.9.4"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    <import addon="script.module.httplib2" />
    <import addon="script.module.liveresolver" version="0.1.24" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.youtube.dl" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" />
    <import addon="script.module.urlresolver" />
	<import addon="script.module.resolveurl" />
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.livestreamer" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.slproxy" optional="true"/>
	<import addon="script.module.simplejson" />
    <import addon="script.module.livestreamer" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pyamf" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
   <extension point="xbmc.service" library="autoexec.py" start="autoexec" />

   <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Mi repositorio">

        <dir>
            <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/picapaujulen/repositorio/master/Repositorio/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/picapaujulen/repositorio/master/Repositorio/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/picapaujulen/repositorio/master/Repositorio/</datadir>
		</dir>

		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>

		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/</datadir>
		</dir>
    </extension>


  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>creado por picapau, lourdes, supertopo y luisma</summary>
    <description>ESTE ADDON NO CONTIENE ENLACES PROPIOS,SON RECOPILACIONES DE LA RED, SOLO SE FACILITA EL ACESSO A ESAS WEBS, ESTAS WEBS SON LAS RESPONSABLES DE LOS CONTENIDOS
	</description>ºº
    <platform>all</platform>
	  <assets>
		<icon>icon.gif</icon>
		<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
	  </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.dplay_dmax_dkiss" name="DPLAY" version="1.1.7" provider-name="Alex303 - Hiraya Software">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Hiraya Software Repo">
		<info>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://hirayasoftware.github.io/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">DPLAY</summary>
		<description lang="en">DPLAY Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Addon con la programación de DPLAY a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<summary lang="es">DPLAY</summary>
		<description lang="es">DPLAY Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Addon con la programación de DPLAY a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
        <website></website>
        <video_guide></video_guide>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.f4mTester" version="2.7.1" name="f4mTester" provider-name="Shani">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.video.F4mProxy" version="2.7.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>


    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>f4mTester</summary>
        <description></description>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.gdrive" version="0.8.66" name="gdrive" provider-name="ddurdle">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video audio image programs</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Listen to music, watch videos and view photos from your Google Drive account</summary>
        <description>Plays music and video from your Google Drive account.  Not affiliated with Google.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login">
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.hbogoeu" name="hGO EU" provider-name="arvvoid" version="2.1.6">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" version="0.1.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.12.4" />
    <import addon="script.module.pycryptodome" version="3.4.3" />
    <import addon="script.module.defusedxml" version="0.6.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.4.2" />
  </requires>
  <extension library="main.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Watch HBO® GO EU+Nordic content in Kodi. Valid HBO® account required.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">
Simple, Kodi add-on to access HBO® Go EU content. (This add-on is not officially commissioned/supported by HBO®.)

Important, HBO® Go must be paid for!!!  You need a valid account!
Register on the official HBO® Go website for your region.

Read the disclaimer!

Curently support: Bosnia and Herzegovina, Bulgaria, Croatia, Czech Republic, Hungary, Macedonia, Montenegro, Polonia, Portugal, Romania, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenija, Spain, Norway, Denmark, Sweden, Finland

To report bugs or request assistence with the add-on go to: https://github.com/arvvoid/plugin.video.hbogoeu
    </description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">
This add-on is not officially commissioned/supported by HBO®. The trademark HBO® Go is registered by Home Box Office, Inc.
For more information on HBO® Go visit the official HBO® Go website for your region.
I do not own any of the content this add-on lists. The content belongs to Home Box Office, Inc.
All this add-on does is make simple HTTP requests to Hbo go servers to retrieve and display content just like any web browser would do!

Important: HBO® Go must be paid for!!! You need a valid HBO® Go account for the add-on to work! Register on the official HBO® Go website for your region

THERE IS NO WARRANTY FOR THE ADD-ON, IT MIGHT NOT WORK AT ALL AND IT CAN BREAK AND STOP WORKING AT ANY TIME.

If an official app is available for your platform, use it instead of this.
    </disclaimer>
    <language>en</language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL-2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=339798</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/arvvoid/plugin.video.hbogoeu</source>
    <website>https://arvvoid.github.io/plugin.video.hbogoeu</website>
    <news>
v.2.1.5
- fix Telekom Romania (My Account) login
- new logo
- fix some encoding errors on log
- better error handling on communication errors
- media info optimizations
    </news>
    <assets>
     <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
     <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
     <screenshot>resources/screen1.png</screenshot>
     <screenshot>resources/screen7.png</screenshot>
     <screenshot>resources/screen8.png</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
	id="plugin.video.koditv" version="2" name="[B][COLOR white]kodi[COLOR aqua]tv[/COLOR][/B]" provider-name="equipo tvchopo">
<requires>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" />
    <import addon="script.module.six" />
  </requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>

	 <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="tvchopo">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/</datadir>
    </extension>


	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
                <platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en"></summary>
		<summary lang="da"></summary>
		<description lang="en"></description>
		<website></website>
		<license>GPL 2.0</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
<assets>
        <icon>icon.jpg</icon>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot1.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot2.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot3.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot4.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot5.jpg</screenshot>
        <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
    </assets>
		<language>es</language>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.mitele" name="MITELE" version="1.3.1" provider-name="Hiraya Software">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
		<import addon="script.module.resolveurl" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Hiraya Software Repo">
		<info>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://hirayasoftware.github.io/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">MITELE</summary>
		<description lang="en">MITELE Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Addon con la programación de MITELE a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<summary lang="es">MITELE</summary>
		<description lang="es">MITELE Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Addon con la programación de MITELE a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
        <website></website>
        <video_guide></video_guide>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.palantir" name="[COLOR gold]Palantir[/COLOR]" version="0.0.79" provider-name="TierraMedia">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="1.9.5"/>
	<import addon="script.module.requests"/>
    <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.extendedinfo" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="orthanc.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Palantir Repo">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Palantiraddon/Repo/master/Palantir/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Palantiraddon/Repo/master/Palantir/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Palantiraddon/repo/master/Palantir/</datadir>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>TV</summary>
    <news>[COLOR lime][B] versión 0.0.79 [/B][/COLOR]
        - [Interno] Compabilidad con el addon GDrive
    </news>
    <description>Visualiza el contenido de la nube, series, películas.</description>
    <disclaimer>[B][COLOR red]Todo el contenido disponible en este Addon esta sacado de servidores gratuitos, disponible en la red para todos los usuarios.[/B][/COLOR]</disclaimer>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
        <fanart>fanart.gif</fanart>
    </assets>
    <license></license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website></website>
    <email></email>
    <source></source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.palantir2" name="[COLOR gold]Palantir 2[/COLOR]" version="2.1.12" provider-name="TierraMedia">
  <requires>
    <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.11.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.0.00" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pycryptodome"/>
    <import addon="script.embuary.info"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Palantir Repo">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Palantiraddon/Repo/master/Palantir/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Palantiraddon/Repo/master/Palantir/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Palantiraddon/repo/master/Palantir/</datadir>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <description>Visualiza el contenido de la nube, series, películas.</description>
    <disclaimer>[B][COLOR red]Todo el contenido disponible en este Addon esta sacado de servidores gratuitos, disponible en la red para todos los usuarios.[/B][/COLOR]</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
        <fanart>fanart.gif</fanart>
        <screenshot>resources/media/Captura1.png</screenshot>
        <screenshot>resources/media/Captura2.png</screenshot>
        <screenshot>resources/media/Captura3.png</screenshot>
        <screenshot>resources/media/Captura4.png</screenshot>
    </assets>
    <news>- Reparados pequeños bugs
    </news>
    <forum>https://t.me/addon_palantir</forum>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.rtve" name="RTVE" version="1.1.5" provider-name="Alex303 - Hiraya Software">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Hiraya Software Repo">
		<info>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://hirayasoftware.github.io/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">RTVE</summary>
		<description lang="en">RTVE Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Addon con la programación de RTVE a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<summary lang="es">RTVE</summary>
		<description lang="es">RTVE Addon</description>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Addon con la programación de RTVE a la carta.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
        <website></website>
        <video_guide></video_guide>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.tvalacarta"
    name="tvalacarta"
    version="4.1.2"
    provider-name="tvalacarta">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="es">Televisión a la carta</summary>
    <description lang="es">Para ver la televisión por Internet, a la carta y desde tu media center</description>
    <summary lang="en">TV on demand (Spanish)</summary>
    <description lang="en">Watch on demand spanish TV on your media center</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GPL v3</license>
    <forum>http://www.mimediacenter.info/foro</forum>
    <website>http://blog.tvalacarta.info/plugin-xbmc/tvalacarta</website>
    <email>tvalacarta@gmail.com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/tvalacarta/tvalacarta</source>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login|startup">
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
	id="plugin.video.tvchopo" version="24" name="[B][COLOR white]tv[COLOR aqua]chopo[/COLOR][/B]" provider-name="equipo tvchopo">
<requires>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" />
    <import addon="script.module.six" />
  </requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>

	 <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="tvchopo">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/</datadir>
    </extension>


	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
                <platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en"></summary>
		<summary lang="da"></summary>
	<description lang="en">[B][LOWERCASE][CAPITALIZE][COLOR white]addon principal de la familia tvchopo, valido para kodi 18 y kodi 19.. este addon es [COLOR red]totalmente gratuito no se aceptan donativos ... no permitas que te vendan este addon.. es  gratis  [COLOR white]..entra en telegram [COLOR gold]@tvchopo[COLOR white] y te ayudamos[/COLOR][/CAPITALIZE][/LOWERCASE][/B]</description>
		<website></website>
		<license>GPL 2.0</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
<assets>
        <icon>icon.jpg</icon>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot1.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot2.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot3.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot4.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot5.jpg</screenshot>
        <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
    </assets>
		<language>es</language>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.Tvchopo.Kids"
       name="[B][LOWERCASE][CAPITALIZE][COLOR white]TVCHOPO[COLOR gold] KIDS[/CAPITALIZE][/LOWERCASE][/B][/COLOR]"
       version="11"
       provider-name="equipo-chopo">
 <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="0.9.4"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    <import addon="script.module.httplib2" />
    <import addon="script.module.liveresolver" version="0.1.24" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.youtube.dl" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" />
    <import addon="script.module.urlresolver" />
	<import addon="script.module.resolveurl" optional="true"/>
	<import addon="script.module.simplejson" />
    <import addon="script.module.livestreamer" optional="true"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pyamf" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>

 <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="tvchoco Jose">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/</datadir>
    </extension>




  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Tvchopo.Kids addon familiar</summary>
    <description>
        addon Tvchopo.Kids no contiene ningun material propio..
		todo el contenido es enlazado a las webs mas conocidas
		de internet.....

	tvchopo ni se vender ni se cobra ni acepta donaciones... si ha sido ese el caso  ha sido usted estafado,...para mas informacion entra en nuestro grupo de telegram @tvchopo

    </description>
    <platform>all</platform>
	<assets>
        <icon>icon.gif</icon>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot1.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot2.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot3.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot4.jpg</screenshot>
  <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot5.jpg</screenshot>
        <fanart>fanart.gif</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.winner" name="[B][/B][COLOR aqua][/COLOR]WINNER" version="1.0.7" provider-name="Camaradas">
    <requires>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" />
        <import addon="script.module.pysocks" />
        <import addon="script.module.six" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" />
        <import addon="script.module.horus" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Hiraya Software Repo">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/camaradas/camaradas.repo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/camaradas/camaradas.repo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/camaradas/camaradas.repo/master/Repositorio/</datadir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">WINNER</summary>
        <description lang="en">Live Sports Addon.

Development: George, Alex303, Picapau
Development support: Jesus, Toni
Contributions: SuperTopo, Jesus
Artwork: Bojbit
Translation: Lou
Content: Lou, Alex303, MiKeL, Chikiry, Bojbit, Luisma, Lucas, Nano, K0S, Manujaz, MrYayi
Testers: Luisma, Toni, Zarat, SuperTopo, Jorge, Bojbit, MiKeL, Chikiry, Pau, Alex, Luar team
        </description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">WINNER Addon - Live Sports Addon</disclaimer>
        <summary lang="es">WINNER</summary>
        <description lang="es">Addon con eventos deportivos en directo.

Desarrollo: George, Alex303, Picapau
Soporte desarrollo: Jesus, Toni
Aportaciones: SuperTopo, Jesus
Artwork: Bojbit
Traducciones: Lou
Contenido: Lou, Alex303, MiKeL, Chikiry, Bojbit, Luisma, Lucas, Nano, K0S, Manujaz, MrYayi
Testers: Luisma, Toni, Zarat, SuperTopo, Jorge, Bojbit, MiKeL, Chikiry, Pau, Alex, equipo Luar
        </description>
        <disclaimer lang="es">Addon WINNER - Eventos Deportivos en directo</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.gif</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.youtube" name="YouTube" version="6.8.15" provider-name="anxdpanic, bromix">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.20.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.11.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.12.4"/>
        <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.2.2" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/startup.py" start="login"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <news>
[fixup] No streams found, consent cookies |contrib: jaylinski|
[fixup] Age gate detection, show age gate error instead of 'No streams found'
[fixup] encoding of some titles/authors - ie. russian
[lang] translation updates from Weblate
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
        <forum>https://ytaddon.panicked.xyz/forum</forum>
        <website>https://www.youtube.com</website>
        <source>https://github.com/anxdpanic/plugin.video.youtube</source>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="bg_BG">Добавка за YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="cs_CZ">Plugin pro YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Plugin für YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Πρόσθετο YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Plugin for YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Plugin para YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="es_MX">Plugin para YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Plugin pour YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="he_IL">תוסף עבור YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="hu_HU">YouTube kiegészítő</summary>
        <summary lang="ko_KR">유튜브 플러그인</summary>
        <summary lang="nb_NO">Tillegg for YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="pl_PL">Wtyczka YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="ru_RU">Видеодополнение YouTube</summary>
        <summary lang="tr_TR">YouTube için eklenti</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_CN">YouTube附加元件</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_TW">YouTube附加元件</summary>
        <description lang="bg_BG">YouTube е един от най-големите уеб сайтове за споделяне на видео в целия свят.</description>
        <description lang="cs_CZ">YouTube je jedna z největších webových stránek světa sdílející video.</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">YouTube ist eines der größten Video-Sharing-Websites der Welt.</description>
        <description lang="el_GR">Το YouTube είναι μία από τις μεγαλύτερες ιστοσελίδες διαμοιρασμού βίντεο στον κόσμο.</description>
        <description lang="en_GB">YouTube is one of the biggest video-sharing websites of the world.</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">YouTube es uno de los sitios web más grande del mundo para compartir vídeos.</description>
        <description lang="es_MX">YouTube es uno de los más grandes sitios web de intercambio de videos del mundo.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">YouTube est l'un des plus grands sites de partage vidéos du monde.</description>
        <description lang="he_IL">YouTube הוא אחד מאתרי שיתוף הווידאו הגדולים בעולם.</description>
        <description lang="hu_HU">A YouTube világ egyik legnagyobb videómegosztó weboldala.</description>
        <description lang="ko_KR">유튜브는 세상에서 가장 큰 동영상 공유 사이트 중의 하나입니다.</description>
        <description lang="nb_NO">YouTube er en av verdens største nettsider for videodeling.</description>
        <description lang="pl_PL">YouTube jest jednym z największych na świecie serwisów udostępniania wideo.</description>
        <description lang="ru_RU">YouTube - популярнейший видеохостинговый сайт, предоставляющий пользователям услуги хранения, доставки и показа видео.</description>
        <description lang="tr_TR">YouTube, dünya üzerindeki en büyük video paylaşma platformlarından birisidir</description>
        <description lang="zh_CN">「Youtube」是全世界最大的影片分享網站</description>
        <description lang="zh_TW">「Youtube」是全世界最大的影片分享網站</description>
        <disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Tento plugin není schválen společností Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Η παρούσα μικροεφαρμογή δεν έχει υϊοθετηθεί από την Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This plugin is not endorsed by Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Este add-on no está respaldado por Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es_MX">Este add-on no está respaldado por Google</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Bu eklenti Google tarafından üretilmemiştir</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh_TW">此附加元件未由Google支持</disclaimer>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="program.plexus"
       name="Plexus"
       version="0.1.8"
       provider-name="tvaddons">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>

  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>SopCast and AceStream for Kodi</summary>
    <description lang="en">Plexus - Any complex structure containing an intricate network of parts. Plexus brings native peer-to-peer support (AceStream and SopCast) for Kodi Entertainment Center for several platforms.[CR][CR]Documentation: (missing)</description>
    <description lang="pt">Plexus - Uma estrutura complexa constituída por uma rede de partes. O Plexus adiciona suporte peer-to-peer nativo (AceStream e Sopcast) ao Kodi Entertainment Center para várias plataformas.[CR][CR]Documentação: (em falta)</description>
    <description lang="es">Plexus - Una estructura compleja conteniendo una intrincada red de partes. Plexus añade soporte nativo peer-to-peer (AceStream y SopCast) al Centro de Entretenimiento Kodi para varias plataformas.[CR][CR]Documentacion: (falta)</description>
	<disclaimer lang="en">The author does not host nor distribute any of the content you may watch using this addon. The author has no part in the development of any included technologies. When seeking help in Kodi's forum please respect rules (http://kodi.wiki/view/Forum_rules).</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Os autores não alojam nem distribuem nenhum do conteúdo que poderá ser reproduzido a partir deste addon. Os autores não têm qualquer parte no desenvolvimento de qualquer uma das tecnologias. Se procurar ajuda no fórum oficial do Kodi por favor respeite as regras do fórum (http://kodi.wiki/view/Forum_rules).</disclaimer>
   	<disclaimer lang="es">El autor no aloja ni distribuye cualquier contenido que ud. pudiera reproducir usando este addon. El autor no tiene participacion en el desarrollo de cualquier tecnologia incluida. Cuando requiera ayuda en el foro de Kodi por favor respete las reglas (http://kodi.wiki/view/Forum_rules).</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
	<forum>https://www.tvaddons.co/forums</forum>
	<website>https://www.tvaddons.co</website>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="pvr.hts"
  version="4.4.21"
  name="Tvheadend HTSP Client"
  provider-name="Adam Sutton, Sam Stenvall, Lars Op den Kamp, Kai Sommerfeld">
  <requires>
<import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
<import addon="kodi.binary.instance.pvr" version="5.10.3"/></requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.pvrclient"
    library_windows="pvr.hts.dll"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Kodi se voorprogram vir Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Клиент за „Tvheadend“</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Frontal de Kodi per a Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Rozhraní Kodi pro Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Blaen Kodi ar gyfer Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Kodis brugerflade til Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Kodi-PVR-Client für Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Το frontend του Kodi για το Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Interfaz Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Interfaz Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">El frontend de Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Kodi liides Tvheadend'ile</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Kodin Tvheadend-asiakasohjelma</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Frontale Kodi pour Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Interface logicielle pour Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Interface do Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">לקוח טלוויזיה חיה עבור Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Kodi sučelje za Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Kodi előtét a TVHeadend-hez</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Frontend Kodi untuk Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Kodi framendi fyrir Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Frontend di Kodi per Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">TVheadend 用 Kodi フロントエンド</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Tvheadend 을 위한 Kodi 프론트엔드</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Kodi naudotojo sąsaja skirta Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Kodi galasistēma Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Kodi's frontend for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="mn_MN">Tvheadend зориулагдсан Kodi-ийн нүүр</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Bahagian hadapan Kodi untuk </summary>
    <summary lang="mt_MT">Faċċata ta' Kodi għat- TVheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Kodis grenseflate for Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Kodi's frontend voor Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Klient telewizji dla Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Frontend Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Interface Kodi para Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Interfața Kodi pentru Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Интерфейс Kodi для Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Kodi rozhranie pre Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Kodijev vmesnik za Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sq_AL">Frontend i Kodi'së për Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS">Kodi-јев интерфејс за Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Kodijev interfejs za Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Kodi's frontend för Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="szl">Frontend do Tvheadend ôd Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="te_IN">Tvheadend కోసం కోడి యొక్క ఫ్రంటెండ్</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_TJ">Интерфейси Kodi барои Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Tvheadend için Kodi ön ucu</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Інтерфейс Kodi для Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Giao tiếp Kodi cho Tvheadend</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">Kodi 的 Tvheadend 前端</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">Kodi的Tvheadend前端介面</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Tvheadend voorprogram; ondersteun stroom van Lewendige TV &amp; Opnames, EPG, Tydhouers</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Клиент за „Tvheadend“. Поддържа телевизия на живо, записване, електронен програмен справочник и броячи.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Frontal de Tvheadend; compatible amb la transmissió de TV en directe i enregistraments, guia electrònica de programació (EPG), temporitzadors</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Rozhraní Tvheadend; podporuje streamování živého vysílání a nahrávání, televizní program, časovače.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Blaen Tvheadend: cefnogi ffrydio Teledu Byw a Recordio, Amserlenni, Amseryddion</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Tvheadend-brugerflade; understøtter streaming af direkte tv og optagelser, EPG og timere</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">PVR-Client für Tvheadend. Unterstützt TV &amp; Aufnahmen, Programm-Guide (EPG) und Timer.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Frontend για το Tvheadend. Υποστηρίζει ροές Live TV &amp; Εγγραφές, EPG, Χρονοδιακόπτες</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Interfaz Tvheadend; soporta la reproducción de TV en vivo, grabación, guía de programación, temporizadores</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Interfaz Tvheadend; soporta la reproducción de TV en vivo, grabación, guía de programación, temporizadores</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Frontend de Tvheadend; Compatible con la transmisión de TV en directo y Grabaciones, EPG, Temporizadores</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">Tvheadend'i liides. Toetab telekanalite striimimist ja salvestamist ning elektroonilist saatekava.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Tvheadend-asiakasohjelma. Tukee suorien tv-lähetysten ja tallennusten katsomista, ohjelmaopasta ja ohjelmien ajastamista.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Frontale pour Tvheadend, prenant en charge la diffusion en continu des télés en direct et les enregistrements, le GÉP et les minuteries</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Interface logicielle pour Tvheadend gérant la lecture en continu de la TV en direct et des enregistrements, le guide électronique des programmes TV et les programmations.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Interface Tvheadend; soporta a transmisión de TV en directo e Gravacións, Guía, temporizadores</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">לקוח טלוויזיה חיה של Tvheadend. תומך בהזרמת שידורים חיים והקלטות, האזנה לרדיו, הצגת לוח שידורים ותזמון הקלטות.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Tvheadend pozadinski softver podržava gledanje i snimanje TV programa, elektronski programski vodič (EPG) i zakazano snimanje.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">TVHeadend előtét. Élő adások és felvételek támogatása EPG-vel és időzítéssel</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Frontend Tvheadend; mendukung menangkap siaran TV Live &amp; Rekaman, EPG, Timer</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Tvheadend framendi; styður streymingu á beinum útsendingum og upptökum, rafrænum sjónvarpsvísum (EGP), tímatökur</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Frontend di Tvheadend; supporta lo streaming di Live TV &amp; Registrazione, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">TVheadend フロントエンドです。ライブTVストリーミング、録画、EPG、タイマーをサポートしています。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">Tvheadend 프론트엔드; TV 시청 &amp; 녹화, EPG, 타이머 지원</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Tvheadend naudotojo sąsaja; palaiko televizijos transliacijas ir įrašus, EPG, laikmačius</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">Tvheadend galasistēma; atbalsta tieštaides TV un ierakstu straumēšanu, EPG, taimerus</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">Tvheadend frontend; supporting streaming of Live TV &amp; Recordings, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="mn_MN">Tvheadend нүүр; Live TV &amp; бичлэг дамжуулалт, EPG, Timer</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Bahagian hadapan Tvheadend; menyokong penstriman  Langsung &amp; Rakaman, EPG, Pemasa TV</description>
    <description lang="mt_MT">Faċċata ta' TVheadend; jiflaħ għal streaming ta' TV Lajv u rekordings, EPG, Arloġġi</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Tvheadend-grenseflate; støtte for visning av direkte-TV og opptak, EPG, tidsur</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Tvheadend frontend. Ondersteuning van streaming, Live-TV &amp; opnames, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Klient telewizji dla Tvheadend obsługuje transmisję kanałów radiowych i telewizyjnych, nagrywanie i harmonogram nagrań oraz funkcje przewodnika telewizyjnego.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Tvheadend; suporta streaming de TV Ao Vivo e Gravada, EPG, Agendamentos</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Interface Tvheadend. Suporta transmissão e gravação de TV em direto, EPG e temporizadores.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Partea din față pentru Tvheadend; suportă difuzarea în flux a televiziunii în direct și a înregistrăriilor, EPG, Cronometre</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Интерфейс для Tvheadend. Поддерживает просмотр и запись ТВ, EPG и таймеры</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Rozhranie pre Tvheadend; je podporované streamovanie živého televízneho vysielania a nahrávok, EPG, časovačov</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Vmesnik za Tvheadend; podpira pretakanje televizije v živo &amp; posnetkov, EPG, časovnike</description>
    <description lang="sq_AL">Tvheadend frotnend përkrahën transmetimin e Live TV'së, EPG'së dhe "timer'ë"</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS">Tvheadend интерфејс; подржава стримовање ТВ Уживо &amp; Снимака, EPG, Тајмере</description>
    <description lang="sr_RS@latin">Tvheadend interfejs; podržava strimovanje TV Uživo &amp; Snimaka, EPG, Tajmere</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Tvheadend frontend; stödjer strömning av Live-TV &amp; inspelningar, EPG, Timers</description>
    <description lang="szl">Frontend Tvheadend; podpiyrŏ strumiyniowaniy TV, nagrań, EPG i minutnikōw</description>
    <description lang="te_IN">Tvheadend ఫ్రంటెండ్; Live TV &amp; రికార్డింగ్స్, EPG, టైమర్లు , స్ట్రీమింగ్ మద్దతు కలదు</description>
    <description lang="tg_TJ">Интерфейси Tvheadend; дастгирии ҷараёни Сабтҳо, Вақтсанҷҳо, Live TV ва EPG</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Tvheadend ön ucu; Canlı TV akışı ve kayıt yapabilme, EPG ve zamanlayıcıları destekler</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Інтерфейс для Tvheadend; підтримує передачу і запис потокового телебачення, EPG (телегід) і таймери.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Giao tiếp cho Tvheadend; hỗ trợ truyền phát và thu chương trình Live TV, hẹn giờ, và hiển thị lịch chiếu (EPG)</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">Tvheadend 前端，支持直播电视和录像流媒体、电子节目单、定时器</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">Tvheadend前端，支援的串流媒體包含有直播電視和錄製節目，電子節目表，定時器 等</description>
    <platform>windows-x86_64</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.alfa-addon" name="[COLOR red]Alfa-Addon[/COLOR] Repo" version="1.0.6" provider-name="Alfa Addon">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Alfa-Addon Repo">
        <info>https://github.com/alfa-addon/alfa-repo/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://github.com/alfa-addon/alfa-repo/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://github.com/alfa-addon/alfa-repo/raw/master</datadir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Repositorio para Alfa-Addon</summary>
        <description></description>
        <disclaimer>The owners and submitters to this repository do not host or distribute any of the content displayed by these addons nor do they have any affiliation with the content providers.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

  <addon id="repository.arvvoid" name="Kodi ArvVoid Repository" version="1.0.0" provider-name="arvvoid">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Kodi ArvVoid Repository">
    <info compressed="false">https://raw.github.com/arvvoid/repository.arvvoid/master/addons.xml</info>
    <checksum>https://raw.github.com/arvvoid/repository.arvvoid/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
    <datadir zip="true">https://raw.github.com/arvvoid/repository.arvvoid/master/</datadir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Kodi ArvVoid Repository</summary>
        <description lang="en">A repository for my Kodi add-ons and add-on test releases.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">THERE IS NO WARRANTY FOR THE ADD-ONS, THEY CAN BREAK AND STOP WORKING AT ANY TIME.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
  </addon>

<addon id="repository.balandro" name="Balandro Repo" version="1.0.5" provider-name="Balandro">
	<requires>
	</requires>

	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Balandro Repo">
        <info>https://balandro.tk/repo3/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://balandro.tk/repo3/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://balandro.tk/repo3</datadir>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Repositorio para Balandro</summary>
        <description>Balandro es un navegador para webs con vídeos de películas y series.</description>
        <disclaimer>The owners and submitters to this repository do not host or distribute any of the content displayed by these addons nor do they have any affiliation with the content providers.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>

</addon>

<addon id="repository.hirayasoftware" name="Hiraya Software" version="1.0.1" provider-name="Alex303 - Hiraya Software">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Hiraya Software">
		<info>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://hirayasoftware.github.io/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://hirayasoftware.github.io/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Hiraya Software Repository</summary>
		<description></description>
		<disclaimer></disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.jsergio" name="jsergio repo" version="1.0.4" provider-name="jsergio">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="jsergio repo">
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Repo for jsergio Add-ons</summary>
		<description>Repo for jsergio Add-ons</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.Maniac" name="Maniac repository" version="1.0.1" provider-name="Maniac">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Maniac Repository">
		<info compressed="false">https://raw.github.com/Maniac2017/repository.Maniac/master/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://raw.github.com/Maniac2017/repository.Maniac/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://raw.github.com/Maniac2017/repository.Maniac/master/repor/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Maniac Addon</summary>
		<description>Repositorio NO oficial para Kodi</description>
		<disclaimer></disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.Palantir" name="[COLOR gold]Palantir[/COLOR] Repo" version="1.0.1" provider-name="TierraMedia">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Palantir Repo">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Palantiraddon/Repo/master/Palantir/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Palantiraddon/Repo/master/Palantir/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Palantiraddon/repo/master/Palantir/</datadir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Repositorio para Palantir</summary>
        <description></description>
        <disclaimer></disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.tvchopo" name="[COLOR lime]tvchopo[/COLOR] Repo" version="2.0.0" provider-name="torete">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="tvchoco Jose">
        <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elchocolate/repotvchopo/master/Repositorio/</datadir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Repositorio para los mios</summary>
        <description></description>
        <disclaimer></disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.atilachecker" name="aTiLaChecker" version="1.0" provider-name="aTiLa">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="startup.py" start="startup" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Comprobador version Build y Parches de WiZaRTiLa</summary>
    <description lang="en"></description>
	<disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="resource.language.es_es"
  version="9.0.23"
  name="Spanish"
  provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="kodi.resource.language"
    locale="es_ES">
    <charsets>
      <gui>CP1252</gui>
      <subtitle>CP1252</subtitle>
    </charsets>
    <sorttokens>
      <token>The</token>
      <token>El</token>
      <token>Los</token>
      <token>La</token>
      <token>Las</token>
      <token>Un</token>
    </sorttokens>
  </extension>
  <extension point="kodi.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Spanish language pack</summary>
    <description lang="en">Spanish version of all texts used in Kodi.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.extendedinfo" name="OpenInfo" version="6.2.4" provider-name="A4K">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
		<import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.2.2"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.service" version="1.0.0"/>
		<import addon="resource.images.studios.white" version="0.0.18"/>
		<import addon="plugin.video.openmeta" version="1.0.0" optional="true"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="script.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="kodi.context.item">
		<menu id="kodi.core.main">
			<item library="context.py">
				<label>OpenInfo</label>
				<visible>String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,season) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,actor) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,director)</visible>
			</item>
		</menu>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<summary>Fork of the ExtendedInfo script from phil65</summary>
		<description>This script offers various possibilities to display online content inside skins as well as a complete MovieDB browser including info dialogs for various media types. Needs skin implementation for lot of functions and OpenMeta for library functions.</description>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot1.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot2.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot3.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<news>
		6.2.4 - Specify param in TV Show ID
		6.2.3 - Fix TV Show trailers
		6.2.2 - Added ability to search using the tvdb_id for "extendedepisodeinfo"
		6.2.1 - Fix context menu now available for widgets pointing to OpenInfo's video addon items
		6.2.0 - Added context menu force "player select" to the play button, available via "c" and long press "enter" button
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.kelebek"
       name="KELEBEK"
       version="3.2.2"
       provider-name="Anabel">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pyxbmct" version="1.1.4" />
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    <import addon="script.module.myconnpy" version="1.1.7"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
	<provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary>KELEBEK V3.2</summary>
    <description>Scan Sources searching changes and addons</description>
    <language></language>
    <license></license>
    <source></source>
    <forum></forum>
    <website></website>
	<assets>
		<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
		<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
	</assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.kodispeedtest"
       name="Test de Velocidad"
       version="0.1.0"
       provider-name="[COLOR lime]Catoal[/COLOR]">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script"
             library="default.py">
        <provides>video executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Test de velocidad</summary>
    <description lang="en"></description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.limpiarkodi"
       name="Limpia Tu Kodi"
       version="2.0.9"
       provider-name="Catoal - Teco">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.11.0"/>
  </requires>
     <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Maniac">
      <info compressed="false">http://raw.github.com/Maniac2017/repository.Maniac/master/addons.xml</info>
      <checksum>http://raw.github.com/Maniac2017/repository.Maniac/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
      <datadir zip="true">http://raw.github.com/Maniac2017/repository.Maniac/master/repor/</datadir>
  </extension>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary>Limpiar</summary>
    <description>La herramienta para limpiar de una pasada su dispositivo.</description>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot000.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot001.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot002.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.logviewer" name="Log Viewer for Kodi" provider-name="i96751414" version="2.1.3+gotham.1">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=223490</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/i96751414/script.logviewer</source>
        <summary lang="en">View Kodi logfile directly on Kodi</summary>
        <summary lang="pt">Veja o log do Kodi directamente no Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="en">Tools to easily check and analyse Kodi log file.</description>
        <description lang="pt">Ferramenta para verificar e ler facilmente o log do Kodi.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <news>
            - Fix Portuguese translations
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot-1.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot-2.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/images/screenshot-3.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.luar"
  version="0.8.1"
  name="Luar"
  provider-name="The Dreamers">
  <requires>
    <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.11.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
    <import addon="resource.language.es_es"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pycryptodome" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Luar Repo">
    <info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Masterwine/Luar/master/repor/addons.xml</info>
    <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Masterwine/Luar/master/repor/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
    <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Masterwine/Luar/master/repor/</datadir>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="es">Script instalador de complementos para Kodi.</summary>
    <description lang="es">Selecciona, instala y disfruta.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="es"></disclaimer>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.gif</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot000.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot001.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot002.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.addon.common"
	     name="Common addon methods"
	     version="2.0.0"
	     provider-name="Eldorado (original: t0mm0)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines</summary>
    <description lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines to simplify addon development.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website></website>
    <email></email>
    <source></source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.beautifulsoup4" name="BeautifulSoup4" version="4.9.3" provider-name="Leonard Richardson (leonardr@segfault.org)">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.soupsieve" version="1.9.6"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Screen-scraping library</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Beautiful Soup is a library that makes it easy to scrape information from web pages. It sits atop an HTML or XML parser, providing Pythonic idioms for iterating, searching, and modifying the parse tree.</description>
		<license>MIT</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<website>https://www.crummy.com/software/BeautifulSoup/</website>
		<source>https://code.launchpad.net/beautifulsoup</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.clouddrive.common" name="Cloud Drive Common Module" version="1.2.12" provider-name="Carlos Guzman (cguZZman)">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.dateutil"/>
		<import addon="script.module.pyqrcode"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="/" />
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Cloud Drive Common Module</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Common Services and Classes for all the cloud drive addons.</description>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מודול משותף לכונן בענן</summary>
		<description lang="he_IL">שירותים ושירותים משותפים לכל התוספים של כונן הענן.</description>
		<license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
		<source>https://github.com/cguZZman/script.module.clouddrive.common</source>
		<forum>https://github.com/cguZZman/script.module.clouddrive.common/issues</forum>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
		<news>
v1.2.12 released Mar 3, 2020:
- NFO export
		</news>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">
This cloud drive addon uses a third-party authentication mechanism commonly known as OAuth 2.0.
If you want to know more about OAuth 2.0 you can visit the following pages:
- https://oauth.net/2/
- https://developers.google.com/identity/protocols/OAuth2
- https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/onedrive/developer/rest-api/getting-started/msa-oauth

Kodi and myself take no responsibility or liability whatsoever.

The authentication server URL is specified in Settings / Advanced / Sign-in Server. The Sign-in Server implements the OAuth 2.0 protocol.
The complete source code of the Sign-in Server can be download here: https://github.com/cguZZman/drive-login
You can clone the project and host it in your own server.
		</disclaimer>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.cryptopy" name="CryptoPy" version="1.2.7" provider-name="cryptopy.sourceforge.net">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon	id="script.module.defusedxml"
		name="defusedxml"
		version="0.6.0"
		provider-name="Christian Heimes">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
		point="xbmc.python.module"
		library="lib" />
	<extension
		point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">defusedxml -- defusing XML bombs and other exploits</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Packed for KODI from https://github.com/tiran/defusedxml</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>PSF</license>
		<website>https://pypi.org/project/defusedxml/</website>
		<source>https://github.com/tiran/defusedxml</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.html5lib"
       name="html5lib-python"
       version="0.999.0"
       provider-name="html5lib">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python"
    		version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.six"
                      version="1.4.1"
                     optional="false"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Standards-compliant library for parsing and serializing HTML documents and fragments in Python.</summary>
    <description>html5lib is a pure-python library for parsing HTML. It is designed to conform to the WHATWG HTML specification, as is implemented by all major web browsers.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <source>https://github.com/html5lib/html5lib-python.git</source>
    <website>https://github.com/html5lib/html5lib-python</website>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.inputstreamhelper" name="InputStream Helper" version="0.5.7" provider-name="emilsvennesson, dagwieers, mediaminister, horstle">
  <requires>
    <!--py3 compliant-->
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pysocks" version="1.6.8" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <!-- This is needed to get an add-on icon -->
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Kodi InputStream and DRM playback made easy</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Kodi InputStream und DRM Wiedergabe einfach gemacht</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Βοηθός Inputstream για το Kodi και εύκολη αναπαραγωγή DRM</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">La lecture Kodi InputStream et DRM en toute simplicité</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Kodi InputStream y reproducción DRM echa fácil</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">A simple Kodi module that makes life easier for add-on developers relying on InputStream based add-ons and DRM playback.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Dieses einfache Kodi-Modul macht das Leben für Addon Entwickler einfacher, die auf InputStream basierte Addons und DRM Wiedergabe angewiesen sind.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Μία απλή μονάδα για το Kodi η οποία διευκολύνει την ζωή των προγραμματιστών οι οποίοι εξαρτώνται από τα πρόσθετσ InputStream και αναπαραγωγή τύπου DRM.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Простой модуль для Kodi, который облегчает жизнь разработчикам дополнений, с использованием InputStream дополнений и воспроизведения DRM контента.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Un simple module Kodi qui simplifie la vie des développeurs de modules complémentaires en s’appuyant sur des modules complémentaires basés sur InputStream et sur la lecture de DRM.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Un módulo Kodi simple que hace la vida más fácil para los desarrolladores de complementos que dependen de complementos basados en InputStream y reproducción de DRM.</description>
    <news>
v0.5.7 (2021-07-02)
- Further improve Widevine CDM installation on ARM hardware

v0.5.6 (2021-06-24)
- Improve Widevine CDM installation on ARM hardware
- Postpone Widevine CDM updates when user rejects

v0.5.5 (2021-06-02)
- Improve Widevine CDM installation on ARM hardware

v0.5.4 (2021-05-27)
- Fix Widevine CDM installation on ARM hardware

v0.5.3 (2021-05-10)
- Temporary fix for Widevine CDM installation on ARM hardware
- Fix Widevine CDM installation on 32-bit Linux

v0.5.2 (2020-12-13)
- Update Chrome OS ARM hardware id's

v0.5.1 (2020-10-02)
- Fix incorrect ARM HWIDs: PHASER and PHASER360
- Added Hebrew translations
- Updated Dutch, Japanese and Korean translations

v0.5.0 (2020-06-25)
- Extract Widevine CDM directly from Chrome OS, minimizing disk space usage and eliminating the need for root access
- Improve progress dialog while extracting Widevine CDM on ARM devices
- Support resuming interrupted downloads on unreliable internet connections
- Reshape InputStream Helper information dialog
- Updated Dutch, English, French, German, Greek, Hungarian, Romanian, Russian, Spanish and Swedish translations
    </news>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://github.com/emilsvennesson/script.module.inputstreamhelper/wiki</website>
    <source>https://github.com/emilsvennesson/script.module.inputstreamhelper</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.kodi-six"
       name="Kodi Six"
       version="0.1.3"
       provider-name="Roman V.M.">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="libs" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Wrappers around Kodi Python API for seamless Python 2/3 compatibility</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Wrappers around Kodi Python API that normalize handling of textual and byte strings in Python 2 and 3.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL v.3</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=327883</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/romanvm/kodi.six</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
    <news>0.1.3:
- Fix non-UTF-8 byte string decoding in Python 2.</news>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.liveresolver"
     name="LiveResolver"
     version="0.1.50"
     provider-name="natko1412">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
    <import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0" />

  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en">Resolve common live video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi + find links embeded in sites.</summary>
    <description lang="en"></description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.myconnpy"
       name="MySQL Connector/Python"
       version="1.1.7"
       provider-name="MySQL">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">MySQL Connector/Python</summary>
        <description lang="en">MySQL Connector/Python is implementing the MySQL Client/Server protocol completely in Python. This means you don't have to compile anything or MySQL (client library) doesn't even have to be installed on the machine.</description>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <website>http://dev.mysql.com/doc/connector-python/en/index.html</website>
        <source>http://dev.mysql.com/downloads/connector/python/</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pyaes"
    name="PyAES"
    version="1.6.1"
    provider-name="ricmoo">

    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
    </requires>

    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Pure-Python Implementation of the AES block-cipher and common modes of operation</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">A pure-Python implementation of the AES (FIPS-197) block-cipher algorithm and common modes of operation (CBC, CFB, CTR, ECB, OFB) with no dependencies beyond standard Python libraries. See README.md for API reference and details.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <website>https://github.com/ricmoo/pyaes</website>
        <source>https://github.com/ricmoo/pyaes</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.pyxbmct"
   name="PyXBMCt"
   version="1.3.1"
   provider-name="Roman V.M.">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.six" />
    <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en_GB">PyXBMCt UI framework</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">PyXBMCt is a mini-framework for simple XBMC addon UI buliding. It is similar to PyQt and provides parent windows, a number of UI controls (widgets) and a grid layout manager to place controls.</description>
    <license>GNU GPL v.3</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=174859</forum>
    <website>http://romanvm.github.io/script.module.pyxbmct/</website>
    <email>roman1972@gmail.com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/romanvm/script.module.pyxbmct</source>
    <news>1.3.1:
- Fix incompatibility with newer Python 3 Kodi builds
- Replace future library with six for Python 3 compatibility</news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.requests"
       name="requests"
       version="2.22.0"
       provider-name="kennethreitz">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.urllib3" version="1.22"/>
    <import addon="script.module.chardet" version="3.0.4"/>
    <import addon="script.module.idna" version="2.6"/>
    <import addon="script.module.certifi" version="2017.07.27.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Python HTTP for Humans</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Packed for KODI from https://pypi.org/project/requests/</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language></language>
    <license>Apache2</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website>http://python-requests.org</website>
    <source>https://github.com/Freso/script.module.requests</source>
    <email>freso.dk AT gmail.com</email>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.resolveurl" name="ResolveURL" version="5.1.35" provider-name="gujal">
    <requires>
        <!-- <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" /> -->
        <import addon="script.module.six" />
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.python.twitch" optional="true" />
        <import addon="plugin.googledrive" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="lib/default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Resolver enlaces a videos de sitios populares para poder reproducirlos en XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju.</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi, simplify addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
        <description lang="el_GR">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi, απλοποίηση της ανάπτυξης των προσθέτων που χρησιμοποιούν πολλαπλούς εξυπηρετητές για υλικό βίντεο</description>
        <description lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju, pojednostavnjuje razvoj priključaka za video dodatke koji zahtjevaju višestruke video izvore.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This script only resolves video content from legitimate file lockers without prejudice. If this script is being used by 3rd parties to resolve content that you feel infringes upon your Intellectual Property then please take your complaints to the actual website or developer linking to such content and not here. This script in no way searches for any content whatsoever.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το ανωτέρο σενάριο το μόνο που κάνει είναι να επιλύει οπτικοακουστικό περιεχόμενο από νόμιμες πηγές χωρίς προκατάληψη. Εάν το ανωτέρο σενάριο χρησιμοποιηθεί από τρίτους ώστε να επιλύσει περιεχόμενο το οποίο σας προκαλεί αντίδραση ότι παραβιάζει την πνευματική σας ιδιοκτησία παρακαλώ μεταφέρετε τα παραπονά σας στον ιστότοπο τον οποίο βρίσκεται το εν λόγω περιεχόμενο η τον δημιουργό ο οποίος πραγματοποιεί την σύνδεση και όχι εδω. Το σενάριο αυτό ουδεμία περίπτωση πραγματοποιεί αναζήτηση περιεχομένου.</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.soupsieve" name="Soup Sieve" version="1.9.6+leia.1" provider-name="Isaac Muse">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.backports.functools_lru_cache" version="1.6.1"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib/" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">A CSS selector library</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Soup Sieve is a CSS selector library designed to be used with Beautiful Soup 4. It aims to provide selecting, matching, and filtering using modern CSS selectors.</description>
		<license>MIT</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<website>https://pypi.org/project/soupsieve/</website>
		<source>https://github.com/facelessuser/soupsieve</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.urlresolver" name="URLResolver" version="5.0.52" provider-name="tvaddons">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.python.twitch" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.cryptopy" version="1.2.6" optional="true" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.gdrive" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="lib/default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Resolver enlaces a videos de sitios populares para poder reproducirlos en XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="hr">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju.</summary>
        <summary lang="el">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi, simplify addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
        <description lang="hr">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju, pojednostavnjuje razvoj priključaka za video dodatke koji zahtjevaju višestruke video izvore.</description>
        <forum>https://www.tvaddons.co/forums</forum>
        <website>https://www.tvaddons.co</website>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.video.F4mProxy" name="F4mProxy" version="2.8.8" provider-name="Shani">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en">Proxy for f4m</summary>
        <description lang="en">Use this addon to play F4m v1 and v2 streams</description>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.xbmc.versioncheck" name="Version Check" version="0.5.8" provider-name="Team Kodi">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/runner.py" start="login"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <news>
- add Kodi 19.0 alpha2 release
- use xbmcvfs for translatePath for matrix
- fix platforms where subprocess is not available
- fix dialogs on Kodi 19
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="be">Kodi Version Check checks if you are running latest released version.</summary>
        <summary lang="bg">Проверява дали ползвате най-новата версия на Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="ca">Kodi Version Check comprova si està utilitzant la última versió publicada.</summary>
        <summary lang="cs">Kontrola verze Kodi, zkontroluje, zda používáte nejnovější vydanou verzi.</summary>
        <summary lang="da">Kodi undersøger om du benytter den nyeste version.</summary>
        <summary lang="de">Kodi Versionsprüfung prüft, ob die neuste Version von Kodi installiert ist.</summary>
        <summary lang="el">Ο Έλεγχος Έκδοσης Kodi εξετάζει αν έχετε την πιο πρόσφατη έκδοση του προγράμματος.</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Kodi Version Check checks if you are running latest released version.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_NZ">Kodi Version Check checks if you are running latest released version.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">Kodi Version Check checks if you are running latest released version.</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Kodi Version Check comprueba si está ejecutando la última versión de Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="es_MX">Comprobador de Version de Kodi comprueba si se esta ejecutando ultima version publicada.</summary>
        <summary lang="fi">Kodi Version Check tarkistaa onko käyttämäsi uusin versio.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Le contrôle de version de Kodi vérifie si la dernière version sortie est utilisée.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">Le contrôleur de version Kodi vérifie si vous utilisez la dernière version parue.</summary>
        <summary lang="gl">Kodi Version Check verifica se está a executar a última versión.</summary>
        <summary lang="he">בודק גרסת Kodi מוודא אם אתה מריץ את הגרסה הרשמית האחרונה.</summary>
        <summary lang="hr">Kodi provjeritelj inačice provjerava imate li posljednju inačicu izdanja.</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">Az Kodi verzió ellenőrző megvizsgálja, hogy a legújabb kiadást futtatja-e.</summary>
        <summary lang="id">Kodi Version Check mengecek apakah Anda menggunakan versi rilis terbaru.</summary>
        <summary lang="is">Kodi Version Check athugar hvort þú sért að keyra nýjustu viðurkennda útgáfu.</summary>
        <summary lang="it">Kodi Version Check verifica se hai l'ultima versione rilasciata</summary>
        <summary lang="ko">Kodi Version Checks는 최신 정식 릴리즈 버전을 사용중인지 검사해줍니다.</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">Kodi Version Check patikrina ar naudojate naujausią versiją.</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Kodi versie-check controleert of je de laatst beschikbare versie hebt.</summary>
        <summary lang="no">Kodi Versjonsettersyn sjekker om du kjører den sist utgitte versjonen.</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Dodatek Version Check sprawdza czy używasz najnowszej wersji Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="pt">O Kodi Version Check verifica se a sua versão de lançamento do Kodi está actualizada.</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Kodi Version Check verifica se você está executando a versão mais recente.</summary>
        <summary lang="ro">Verificare versiune Kodi verifică dacă folosiți ultima versiune lansată.</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Kodi Version Check проверяет если вы используете последнюю версию</summary>
        <summary lang="sk">Kodi Kontrola verzií overuje, či používate najnovšiu vydanú verziu.</summary>
        <summary lang="sl">Preverjanje različice Kodi preveri, če imate nameščeno nazadnje izdano različico.</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Kodi Version Check kontrollerar om du använder den senaste versionen.</summary>
        <summary lang="tr">Kodi Sürüm Kontrol yayınlanmış son sürümü kullanıp kullanmadığınızı kontrol eder.</summary>
        <summary lang="zh">Kodi 版本检查检查你使用的是否为最新发布的版本。</summary>
        <description lang="be">Kodi Version Check only supports a number of platforms/distros as releases may differ between them. For more information visit the kodi.tv website.</description>
        <description lang="bg">Kodi Version Check поддържа няколко платформи/дистрибуции. За повече информация посетете страницата www.kodi.tv</description>
        <description lang="ca">Kodi Version Check només és compatible amb una sèrie de plataformes / distribucions ja que les ultimes versions poden ser diferents entre elles. Per obtenir més informació, visiteu el lloc web kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="cs">Kontrola verze Kodi podporuje pouze několik platforem/distribucí a verze mezi nimi se můžou lišit. Pro více informací navštivte webové stránky kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="da">Kodi kan kun undersøge for opdateringer for visse platforme/udgaver, da der kan være forskel. For mere information, besøg kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="de">Kodi Versionsprüfung unterstützt nur ein paar Plattformen/Distributionen, da sich die jeweiligen Veröffentlichungen unterscheiden können. Für weitere Informationen besuchen Sie die kodi.tv-Webseite.</description>
        <description lang="el">Ο Έλεγχος Έκδοσης Kodi υποστηρίζει μόνο ορισμένα λειτουργικά συστήματα/διανομές, καθώς οι εκδόσεις διαφέρουν για το καθένα. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες επισκεφθείτε το kodi.tv</description>
        <description lang="en">Kodi Version Check only supports a number of platforms/distros as releases may differ between them. For more information visit the kodi.tv website.</description>
        <description lang="en_NZ">Kodi Version Check only supports a number of platforms/distros as releases may differ between them. For more information visit the kodi.tv website.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">Kodi Version Check only supports a number of platforms/distros as releases may differ between them. For more information visit the kodi.tv website.</description>
        <description lang="es">Kodi Version Check solo soporta un número limitado de plataformas/distribuciones, ya que los lanzamientos pueden diferir entre ellos. Para más información, visite la web de kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="fi">Kodi Version Check tukee vain joitain alustoja/distroja koska julkaisut saattavat poiketa toisistaan. Saadaksesi lisätietoa, vieraile kodi.tv:ssä.</description>
        <description lang="fr">Le contrôle de version de Kodi ne prend en charge qu'un certain nombre de plate-formes/distributions car les versions peuvent varier entre elles. Pour plus d'informations, consulter le site Web kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="fr_CA">Le contrôleur de version Kodi ne prend en charge qu'un certain nombre de plate-formes/distributions car les versions peuvent varier entre elles. Pour plus d'informations, visitez le site Web kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="gl">Kodi Version Check só soporta un número limitado de plataformas/distribucións, xa que os lanzamentos poden diferir entre eles. Para máis información visitar o sitio web de kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="he">בודק גרסת Kodi תומך רק במספר פלטפורמות/הפצות מאחר שסימון הגרסאות שונה בין אחת לשניה. למידע נוסף בקר באתר kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="hr">Kodi provjeritelj inačice samo podržava broj platformi/distribucija koliko to dopuštaju pojedina izdanja. Za više informacija posjetite kodi.tv web stranicu.</description>
        <description lang="hu">Az Kodi verzió-ellenőrző csak néhány platformot / disztribúciót támogat, mert a kiadások között különbségek lehetnek. További információkért keresse fel az kodi.tv oldalt.</description>
        <description lang="id">Kodi Version Check hanya mendukung beberapa platform/distro karena rilisnya mungkin berbeda-beda. Untuk informasi lebih lanjut kunjungi situs kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="it">Kodi Version Check supporta un numero di piattaforme e distribuzioni diverse tra loro. Per più informazioni visita il sito kodi.tv</description>
        <description lang="ko">Kodi Versio Check는 일부 플랫폼/배포본만을 지원합니다. 자세한 정보는 kodi.tv 웹사이트에서 확인하세요</description>
        <description lang="lt">Kodi Version Check palaiko tik kelias platformas/distribucijas, nes leidimai tarp jų gali skirtis. Norėdami gauti daugiau informacijos, apsilankykite Kodi.tv puslapyje.</description>
        <description lang="nl">Kodi versie check ondersteunt alleen een aantal platforms/distro`s omdat uitgaven verschillen tussen hen. Voor meer informatie bezoek de kodi.tv website.</description>
        <description lang="no">Kodi Versjonsettersyn støtter kun noen plattformer/distribusjoner fordi utgivelser kan være forskjellige mellom dem. Besøk kodi.tv for mer informasjon.</description>
        <description lang="pl">Dodatek Version Check wspiera tylko część platform i dystrybucji. Więcej informacji na stronie kodi.tv</description>
        <description lang="pt">O Kodi Version Check suporta apenas algumas plataformas/distribuições, porque os lançamentos podem não ser sempre idênticos. Para mais informação, visite o site kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Verificador de versões do Kodi somente suporta algumas plataformas/distros em que os lançamentos podem diferenciar entre si. Para maiores informações visite o website kodi.tv.</description>
        <description lang="ru">Проверка новых версий Kodi поддерживается только на ряде платформ/дистрибутивов и они могут различаться между собой. Для получения доп. информации посетите сайт kodi.tv</description>
        <description lang="sl">Preverjanje različice Kodi podpira le nekatere platforme/distribucije, saj se izdaje med njimi lahko zelo razlikujejo. Za več informacij obiščite spletišče kodi.tv</description>
        <description lang="sv">Kodi Version Check stöder endeast ett antal plattformar/distributioner eftersom utgivningar kan skilja mellan dessa. För mer information besök kodi.tv webplatsen.</description>
        <description lang="tr">Kodi Sürüm Kontrol sürümler arasında değişiklik olduğu için sadece birkaç platform/dağıtım destekler. Daha fazla bilgi için kodi.tv web sitesini ziyaret edin.</description>
        <description lang="zh">Kodi 版本检查只支持部分平台/发行版，它们之间的版本可能会有所不同。欲了解更多信息，请访问 kodi.tv 网站。</description>
        <disclaimer lang="be">Feel free to use this script. For information visit kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="bg">Ползвайте скрипта свободно. За повече информация посетете www.kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ca">Sigues lliure d'utilitzar aquest script. Per més informació visita kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="cs">Neváhejte použít tento skript. Pro více informací navštivte kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="da">Du er velkommen til at bruge dette script. For information, besøg kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de">Zögern Sie nicht, dieses Skript zu verwenden. Für Informationen besuchen Sie kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el">Χρησιμοποιήστε αυτό το script ελεύθερα. Για πληροφορίες επισκεφθείτε το kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Feel free to use this script. For information visit kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Feel free to use this script. For information visit kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_US">Feel free to use this script. For information visit kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es">Puede usar libremente este programa. Para más información, visite kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es_MX">Sientase libre de utilizar este script. Para mas información visita kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr">Utiliser ce script si désiré. Pour plus d'informations, consulter le site kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">N'hésitez pas à utiliser ce script. Pour plus d'informations visitez kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="gl">Síntase libre de usar este script, para máis información visitar kodi.tv.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="he">תרגיש חופשי להשתמש בסקריפט זה. למידע נוסף בקר ב-kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hr">Slobodno koristite ovu skriptu. Za više informacija posjetite kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hu">Használja bátran ezt a szkriptet! Információkért keresse fel az kodi.tv oldalt!</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="id">Jangan sungkan menggunakan script ini. Untuk informasi hubungi kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="it">Usa liberamente lo script. Per informazioni visita kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ko">이 스크립트를 자유롭게 사용하세요. 관련 정보는 kodi.tv를 방문하세요.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="lt">Galite laisvai naudoti šį scenarijų. Apsilankykite kodi.tv, norėdami gauti daugiau informacijos.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="nl">Gebruik dit script vrijblijvend. Voor meer informatie bezoek kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="no">Du har fri tillatelse til å benytte dette skriptet. Besøk kodi.tv for informasjon</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pl">Zapraszamy do używania tego dodatku. Więcej informacji na stronie kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt">Esteja à vontade para usar este script. Para mais informação, visite kodi.tv.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Sinta-se livre para usar este script. Para maiores informações visite kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ro">Simțiți-vă liberi să folosiți acest script. Pentru informații vizitați kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ru">Используйте этот скрипт на свое усмотрение. Для информации посетите kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sl">Izvolite uporabiti ta skript. Za dodatne informacije obiščite kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sv">Använd gärna detta skript. För information, besök kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="tr">Bu betiği kullanmaktan çekinmeyin. Daha fazla bilgi için kodi.tv adresini ziyaret edin</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh">可放心使用此脚本，更多信息访问 kodi.tv</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later, GPL-3.0-or-later, Apache-2.0</license>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=160228</forum>
        <website>https://kodi.tv</website>
        <source>https://github.com/XBMC-Addons/service.xbmc.versioncheck</source>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
